Traitors or heroes?
Wasp Network is a drama, history, thriller film directed by Olivier Assayas.
Havana, Cuba, 1990.
René González, an airplane pilot, unexpectedly flees the country, leaving behind his wife Olga and his daughter
Irma, and begins a new life in Miami, where he becomes a member of an anti-Castro organization.
Olga, played by Penélope Cruz.
René, played by Edgar Ramírez.
Viramontez, played by Gael García Bernal.
Ana Margarita, played by Ana de Armas.
Roque, played by Wagner Moura.
Basulto, played by Leonardo Sbaraglia.
Wasp Network is a 2019 spy thriller film written and directed by Olivier Assayas,
based on the book The Last Soldiers of the Cold War by Fernando Morais.
It stars Penélope Cruz, Édgar Ramírez, Gael García
Bernal, Ana de Armas, and Wagner Moura.
It tells the true story of Cuban spies in American territory during the 1990s.
The film had its world premiere at the Venice Film Festival on 1 September 2019.
It was released in France on 31 January 2020 by Memento Films,
and was released on 19 June 2020 by Netflix.
The film explores themes of miami, florida, cuba, espionage, spy, terrorism.
The tone is emotional and intense.